Bogdan Putiak

Front-End Developer

PROFILE

A graduate in applied linguistics seeking opportunities for development as a junior specialist. I have solid 2 years of programming experience, with a particular emphasis on advanced skills in JavaScript and ReactJS.

I am enthusiastic about professional development in the programming field and ready to contribute my skills to a new team. I am confident that my experience, determination, and skills align with the expectations for the position of a Junior Front-End specialist.

EXPERIENCE

JustSchool, **Remote**— English Tutor

MARCH 2023 - SEP 2023.

ChebaBud, Remote — Salesman, Facebook Ads Specialist, Front-end Dev

JUN 2023 - PRESENT.

LunarLogic, On site— Front-end Developer with React (Trainee)

OCT 2023 - APR 2024.

PROJECTS

Spotify Music Controller – *Django / React / Material UI* <u>GitHub Repo</u>

- Connects to Spotify API using DRF.
- UI developed with React and Material UI.
- Allows users to join chat rooms to vote for the next song.

GymBro Website — React / SCSS / HTML <u>Live</u>

- Demonstrates proficiency in React.
- Utilizes HTML, SCSS, and React best practices.
- Structured and styled for functionality and visual appeal.

CONTACT ME -

<u>■ bogdanputiak@gmail.com</u>

inLinkedIn

Q Warsaw, Poland

GitHub

+48 451 008 269

Portfolio

EDUCATION

Lviv Polytechnic National University — Applied Linquistics

SEP 2021 - MAY 2022



SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Python

Frontend: HTML, CSS / SCSS, CSS modules / Styled components, MUI

← Frameworks / libraries: React.js, React Router, Redux
Toolkit

👉 Data Fetching: Axios / Fetch, Rest API

← Backend: Django REST Framework, Node.js, Express.js

Database: PostgreSQL

Version control: Git, GitHub

COURSES

"Python generation": Course for advanced.

← Harvard CS50 Course



LANGUAGES

👉 Ukrainian - Native

👉 Polish - Level B1